DRU SANCHEZ

Sacramento, CA 95814

Phone: (530)329-2174 | Email: Drubaloo@Outlook.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andru-sanchez-465696194/ | Github: https://drubaloo.github.io/Portfolio/

SUMMARY

I am a Software Engineer with a history of business leadership, customer satisfaction, and many abilities including HTML, CSS, and Javascript. As a graduate of the UC Davis Coding Bootcamp, I'm currently pushing myself to apply my experience with embracing challenges and providing the best product available. As a business manager, I was able to raise profits by 15% in 2019 while training and leading a team of employees. As a Software Engineer, I bring excellent communication, time management, and planning skills as an experienced leader. I am prepared to push myself, grow, and build phenomenal applications that exceed client expectations.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

PROJECTS

Up-Above | https://github.com/Drubaloo/Up-Above | https://drubaloo.github.io/Up-Above/

- A minimalistic website to get the NASA picture of the day and information about our planets.
- Management of Git repo and JS overseeing
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Weather-Dashboard | https://github.com/Drubaloo/Weather-Dashboard https://github.com/Drubaloo/Weather-Dashboard

- An easy view to get weather information using the OpenWeather API
- Complete design and functionality
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Batman Quiz | https://github.com/Drubaloo/Trivia-Quiz

https://drubaloo.github.io/Trivia-Quiz/

- A fun game to test your knowledge of Batman
- Complete design and functionality
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager The Sandwich Spot

2015 – Present Yuba City, Ca Responsible for day to day operation of the business and training new employees to represent the business to the best of their abilities.

Key Accomplishments:

- Took over management of the store so that owners can live off-site and not have to worry.
- Raised profit income by 15% in 2019.
- Trained over 10 employees to successfully represent our values

Closing Manager Steele House Coffee

2017 - 2018

Yuba Citv. Ca

Responsible for the preparation and serving of beverages for customers as well as cleaning and securing the building at the end of the night.

Key Accomplishments:

- Helped train all new employees
- Helped start the business and prepare to bring a new small business to our little town
- Launched a successful business to grow and succeed when I left it

Administrative Assistant The City of Live Oak

2014 - 2015

Yuba Citv. Ca

Responsible for helping citizens with issues and payments regarding their accounts with the city while planning events and overseeing the local public pool

Key Accomplishments:

- Organized city events to operate without any complications.
- Developed flyers and other advertisements for upcoming events and organizations.

EDUCATION

UC Davis, Sacramento, Ca

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Degree or Certification: UC Davis, Sacramento, Ca

Yuba College, Marysville, Ca 2011 - 2013

Yuba City Charter High School, Yuba City, Ca 2009-2011

Graduated early as class valedictorian